linkit.com 2016-10-12

# Origami - WordPress HTML -

## General

Your privacy is important to us. This privacy policy applies to Web sites operated by Advanced Assessments Systems, Inc (DBA LinkIt! Software) (collectively, the "Sites"), including:  
linkit.com   
portal.linkit.com  
or any sub-domains: [name].linkit.com

This privacy policy generally explains the type of information we collect through our Web sites and how we use that information. PLEASE NOTE, HOWEVER, THAT THIS POLICY DOES NOT APPLY TO PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE STUDENT INFORMATION FURNISHED THROUGH THE SITES, OR BY ANY OTHER MEANS, IN CONNECTION WITH OUR SOFTWARE APPLICATIONS AND SERVICES PROVIDED TO OUR CUSTOMERS. SUCH PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION IS GOVERNED BY A SEPARATE POLICY.

## Information Collection

At the Sites, we offer you the opportunity to request information about our products, programs and services. We also allow visitors to request, by email, information about becoming a partner. We may also collect the following types of personally identifiable information through the Sites: the email address of visitors, user-specific information regarding what pages visitors access or visit and other information that visitors to the Sites may submit, such as registration information. 

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our Web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape or Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows 2000 or Mac OS), the domain name of your Internet service provider (ISP) and your computer's IP address. 

## How We Use The Information

We use this information to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and other questions or comments you submit to us. We also may use the personally identifiable information that we collect to offer you other products or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

We may use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our Site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze Site usage.

We do not normally use IP addresses to identify individual users, but may do so if we feel that there are or may be safety and/or security risks. We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena, in response to a law enforcement agency request, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms and Conditions of Use, or as otherwise required by law. In addition, we may transfer information to a third party in the event of a sale, merger or other transfer of all or substantially all of the assets of LinkIt! Software.

## Choices / Opt-Out

As noted above, LinkIt! Software may contact you to provide you with opportunities to purchase products or services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive marketing information from this Site or that we not share your information with any third party, just let us know by sending us an email at privacy@linkit.com 

## Collection of Information by Others

The Sites contain links to third-party Web sites (e.g., to our publishing partners' Web sites) whose information practices may be different than ours. This privacy policy does not apply to Web sites of any other company or organization linked to a LinkIt! Software site. You should consult the other Sites' privacy notices, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. 

## Security

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. 

## Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy notice or its implementation, you may contact us at privacy@linkit.com or contact us via postal mail at the following address: 

LinkIt! Software  
80 Fifth Ave, Suite 1104  
New York, NY 10011  
Attention: Privacy
